

SELVANA **NAGUIB**

UI/UX Designer

CONTACT ME

Email Address: selvana naguib4@gmail.com

Website: www.selvana-naguib.com

Mobile Number: 01211747667

Address: Sheraton Elmatar, Cairo,

ABOUT ME

I am a multidisciplinary designer with a curious mind, I enjoy to meet new people and understand how they are solving problems, this is one of the reasons why I invest my time on meetups from product management to everything related to design (research, design thinking, design system, etc.) and talking to people in general, as always can be an opportunity to learn something new.

EDUCATION

Bachelor

2016

Computer Science and Information Systems, Helwan University

School

2012

Hafez Ibrahim Experimental Language School

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior UI/UX Designer at Egabi (Sahab/SDO)

November 2021 – November 2023

Senior UI/UX Designer at Arabian Systems (Emirates Auction) October 2020 – November 2021

UI/UX Designer at eBenefits Network

July 2018 - September 2020

UI/UX Designer at Agile Technologies

March 2017 - July 2018

UI / UX Designer at Alexon Development

June 2016 - March 2017

RESPONSIBILITY

- Collaborate with Business Analysts to gather and assess user requirements.
- Use storyboards, process flows, and sitemaps to illustrate design concepts.
- Create UI mockups and prototypes to demonstrate site functionality and appearance.
- Develop and maintain product style guidelines.
- Design original graphics, including images, fonts, colors, and animations, using tools like Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, Sketch, Figma, and Principle.
- Identify and resolve UX issues, such as responsiveness.
- Adjust layouts based on user feedback.
- Upload designs to Zeplin for developer implementation.
- Wireframe and design websites, as well as Android and iOS applications, using Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch, and Balsamiq.
- Implement designs using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap.
- Create company logos, banners, and brochures.

SKILLS

Technical Skills

- Figma:	•	•	•	•	•
- Adobe XD:	•	•	•	•	•
- Sketch:	•	•	•	•	•
- Photoshop:	•	•	•	•	•
- Principle:	•	•	•	•	•
- Balsamiq:	•	•	•	•	•
- Invision:	•	•	•	•	•
- Zeplin:	•	•	•	•	•
- Illustrator:	•	•	•	•	0
- HTML:	•	•	•	0	0
- CSS:	•	•	•	0	0
- Bootstrap:	•	•	•	0	0

Personal Skills

Personal Skills					
- Problem Solving:	•	•	•	•	•
- Adaptation:	•	•	•	•	•
- Representation:	•	•	•	•	•
- Team Working:	•	•	•	•	•
- Working under Stress:	•	•	•	•	•
- Attention to Details:	•	•	•	•	•
- Flexability:	•	•	•	•	•
- Willing to Learn:	•	•	•	•	•
- Hard Working:	•	•	•	•	•

LANGUAGES

Arabic / English

INTERESTS

Travelling / Acting / Drawing / Swimming

PROJECTS

Egabi (Sahab/SDO)

- Digital Sharjah
- Civil Defense

Arabian Systems (Emirates Auction)

- Emirates Auction Website, Android & IOS Mobile Apps
- Command Center Website
- Almogayem Website
- Emirates Road Assistance Android & IOS Mobile Apps
- Providal Portal Android & IOS Mobile Applications

eBenefits Network

- eBenefits Network Websites
- G&M Dashboard Website
- Quick Base Website
- Benefit Mall Website
- Idea Consult Website
- eBN Market Place
- No Code Mapping Tool
- SBA Loans Website
- Vive Website, Android & IOS Mobile Applications
- Felmie Website, Android & IOS Mobile Applications
- Logos, Brochures & Banners

Agile Technologies

- Kuwait Capital of Arab Youth Website & Mobile Apps
- ETender Website
- CMA (Contract System with Chatbot)
- Agile Portal Website & Mobile Applications
- Dry Clean Website, Dashboard & Mobile Applications
- Logos, Brochures & Banners

Alexon Development

- eCommerce Website & Mobile Applications
- Saudi Post Mobile Applications

Freelance Projects

- Payment Gateway Mobile Applications
- Tickets Mobile Applications
- Paysky Website
- Car Dealer Website
- D Writing Mobile Applications
- Chorus Mobile Applications

Graduation Project

- Health Care Cloud Computing

PORTFOLIO

Please Check my Portfolio http://www.selvana-naquib.com/#portfolio